In.
It
a little. Am
. I an end.
To an elite and. A half.
A century is
a found these have been the most rich
in all Manson Mr. It is always been
a magnet and they are the scholar
of the sport and the adventure.
I. Took. Them in my house I come
up. To check.
Have. Gone violent but possibly
uninhabited since the beginning
of the. Day I want to live on
a beautiful island like
that mother so. You
know this may sound crazy but I
got announced that if you get
a notion into one it's crazy all right you
had like to get out and I'm like that
was nothing but
a tough problem with we're on our way to
do tigers and so much and I want to be God
I don't have to kill to get
a fellow I'd like to get out and I would
like this and fight the battle with make
sure against man with my bare
hands. And well it was out of my
windows like this that Robinson brutally
exactly what I mean Robinson Crusoe in the
midst of make
a mockery out of you when you've been
living behind the woodshed so many years to
be crying. Out your play but beyond my
mouth I were only thinking of things like
this I said what you want is about the
Edge of Time that when you get back you'll
find me living in a penthouse. Going
On and off there's a lever twice
a day now that you're. On these islands
when we got back we'll find you tied to
a stake and be the remnants of a shortage.
But you want that you look like
a man and out make
a sound in real money and I'll bet you're
young protege happy right now when I'm on
the this is the best I've met you when you
get back I'll be living the life you bet
. The tiger was saying that right
that's right good. Luck just act and
cause Propofol I'm all.
Wet two weeks enjoy my. Back I
have no time to second straight.
Day How about that dog or rather than
come. Back don't have that don't.
Follow my all. You win that bet on
a guy and you tend to think. I've got
something up my sleeve. You'll be up.
To the bank on picking up the
next time I. Expected that.
We would suddenly and for now. Come
up to the world for many many months.
Ago the first thing to
do is look for water.
Thank you water. Let's go.
Right along. I thought I had. Tried. It.
Little brackish but not
bad at all one side. In
a way that I'm going to one more chance.
Oh God. Fresh water for colors.
For one.
AM When is it and when
a new name in
a. Few months have now passed.
Along with the police
even the situation like
this is almost one gulp.
In an.
Image. And try to.
Get on a high when I want
to go and definitely. Not
a. Dime strike more adaptable
than the whole lot into.
A man and and woman.
Pretty smart Runic now you're saying you
have your great grandmother. Running
here looking at you.
Now have atomic weight.
I'm
a fanny fighting bad life certainly not
going to starve I was. Our man camelback
young. Coming on. When I heard and read
through. Temple. I'm
also and I want to argue
I do not want to die. Out for
a place to live. To
new.
And to.
Park Avenue on it especially second
Street and an auto not show or will show.
A boy is going to stir it next
thing to the next generic job. Or.
On going to show you
a little trick with down ten fifteen
or two hundred on your little. Putting
a band in the Sunday Times place
like playing in your new position.
Then got shot believe God only
maybe not the first impulse.
Was not. The minimum number.
This is but
a lot really navies of these islands make
rope out of this in various other things
. And.
Even really I suppose you know one more I
got all this information. Well I've been
a Boy Scout and I've read
Dan there's Hannibal.
This is labor saving devices known to man.
Use the one hundred ways. Ways to go to.
Jail no schools no fights
nothing to deceive you.
To know this temperamental
change old man knowing God.
Isn't.
Going to be
a cinch didn't make your
old one night your time. I
think about I want to get County we have
got a house and spite of my own and
a neighbor in.
It isn't that it's totally different.
Geographically and in vegetation from our
Robinson Crusoe I. Was.
Going on this I was. Evidently
does not want to take up. My
Space. And. To take. Me To You
know what this is possible so.
That the camps have come to the
man he is supposed to man. Said as
a token of the take. These
guys is going to have.
Them is probably the girl's mother. She's
a good match for the son in law all right
all right all right. That would be to
wear out after several months all right
the natives say out before and I have to
wait and the galleys be buying up right
dress down and down the hall the groom to
be let up on to come keep us out of the
ups and knocks out our phone. No kidding
actual fact or will we do the same thing
only we usually weeks until after the
service.
And.
Oh Harry.
To.
The. End of.
The. Well. I
mean never become mentally
down and that meant to be
a. Come.
I fancy one.
Local.
Boy that's what I call it because
over the only stopping off at about
a greyhound ran up your lap.
That was just to find cracks under
any material and move the T.V.
Wandering around in one of the
disruptions little cars already got.
I. Mean I cannot
live. Out of work without
a head shot. Onboard time put in
a. Good one you are not
will kill me putting
you know our power to.
The full.
Senate. In
an. In in.
Terms of.
Where your man is God to
attach something to Soapy ran.
Into. The Senate.
Well known as. Gone.
Fishing.
Out really. Only one face.
You got a little bit of
a lack of. Low
tide nothing new to me said yesterday.
The product is much Family
Robinson. The guide to.
Track number told. Prescott.
How lucky I was to I was wondering where
we were going to get our product.
The tabloids are living out your
to peel away your work to feel.
Like you're.
Having.
Your down or. Out of their.
And. On and on and.
On and. The
animals an. Awful lot of.
Talk about.
Her or her or her.
And I didn't.
Know or you were going to do.
Err. Marry
a lawyer. Am
I a C.N.N.
The now where
a heavy eight is.
A. Rare.
Well.
For. The old
world as. It is in the.
City. It is.
In. The the.
New.
The
event
the
root of the is
one.
New. Moon.
I.
Shall. Say.
I. Want to play.
Don't think I understand you're going to
be my side of. Science can prove right.
Now that this second spray
was several. I think about.
How. I thought you would be confined.
To.
Gotchas famous toehold in my own
camera locked there like that.
Would be good though.
This hurts me worse than it does
you know. You feel that way about.
Of the curator of the work of one of. Our
behavior. You must be Friday the
thirteenth.
On the right the operator used to
tell the radio announcer. I got
a notion that might be crazy.
Radio to me thanks copper loudspeaker
radio idea will become the first real
contribution to our better
quality pictures in. The swamp.
To.
You to.
Fly one on how you.
Met.
Come back yet you.
Accept. To.
Lose. Lose in.
The end it has.
No I don't think Robin Crusoe
had anything like this.
And I'm going to read that book again. In.
Friday's gong. You must be starting.
I've.
Written in
is
in it and is in you.
In it is.
In.
Your bed and is. Coming
where did you come from.
To one who. Whoa kamiński hair.
Done again it will stay. Away from K.
Ome friends. Did you swear.
To paddle
a canoe. Oh crap. I'm not an. Owner
and I knew there. Was what I'd like to
stop. Way we were expecting
everyone here. And
I got
a Grand Rapids. And
I make an exchange that.
This robot. That
bed is only here. I wanted
it this week you want to.
I like that.
Well. There's that.
Far thank God.
They can. Go thanking the news of
the day during the month of October
every hundred sixty people were injured
at forty three were killed I don't think
that's not commit. George
Graham it's after jumping from
a story with the police get
off everything it was. John.
Guy
a capitalist with the neighbors but your
family so he is spending the next six months
in jail. This
program is sponsored by the Dawson Cobb
cosmetic company now don't forget to get
out if you want to be beautiful if you
want to be an awfully early start because
famous nit pick dopy PA say besides
our pencils don't think save us that
a concrete and don't because they might.
Like to hear the charge
current more because that's.
An accomplice
a dime for all I know that I'm
going to be glad that I had. You
know I was job. This week.
For the. Sleepy.
Old. Bandit I sleep out here.
To spend. The night.
You don't piss down. What do you do. Only.
I had. No.
Knowledge. Of the night.
I've been drinking. I'm not.
Some day.
In the.
The the the the.
The better this is where you begin this
little game of mine why not some of these
natives not show you how I'm going to win
that bet but Mr Robinson. I like. On our
way to make.
That's right gotta be. Honest
I've got to say I have.
Never never ever see one
a man is punished you can still
watch but never talk. You
can have both Number two.
I have been where you are now or even
actually the reason why I think like.
This is the one who calls the
cops. On the city doing its job.
I'm not going to. I'm
I was. In
a not. Very good so. I'm
yes. Yes yes. Yes.
Yes.
Same an island. Where. I was.
I don't. Know no no all women
ever need to know.
That it isn't going fine
then I think you know the.
One night Laurie. Perfectly that Biden God
is inspiring and.
All silver sweet. I don't like
his music to ascend.
Heavenly night I'm appear to
being a biologist with
a brain to black women with the. No
. I.
Absolutely I think. I did. The clock
was to come back and I didn't
know we must go next
a spot. That's
great Mike real kind of how it was
that's the only up to do man on
island
a little bagel can. I just
take it around because
.
He's. A little.
Ham.
That is
a young. Adult mom every conductor
on but this is an impossible
situation. It's so sudden you
know even though my family.
Decided they not like it when
I come. It's so different. I
run out. And.
Thank. God it's
the posse. You see Saturday where
Savage is your accomplice miles
peaceful people we have football Price
thanks to. The press you play bridge.
And. No sanity.
I would spoil your being with
a friend in the world. This is. All
off.
My grandfather. Air. With him.
In.
The air in the air.
Given the memories.
With.
In his genuine
Aneurin entered into an
N.F.L.
After.
You know way too.
Erica.
We have.
Saturday. Check
a contract. I got to
figure out something. To
.
All the comforts of Devon your.
Clothes Your
a lot of weight. On. Saturday
Saturday my friend I've. Got
just in time probably because I.
Want to keep. The bad.
White looks as though you have everything
in the bank you haven't seen anything yet
.
I'd like to. The man in.
The exit polls who got it all moved out.
That would.
Never occur to me I like that
some other. Complication. Another
complication. Of My Time flies if I am
we've got going on here quick take the
monkey to talk to the parents. Of Bell South
of the nothing unexpected I got out of
this with the onset I will come when I'm.
Done and I've got to.
Get up. Out of nothing.
But I'm stuck up
a few feet down I'm going
in and out of power. M.
.
S.
Two thousand bucks. I
knew.
This is a question. Because it has
a name you should have you know I've got
to go back and you should've stayed on
island. And you're watching the
daughter eat what you're going to do as
a rule being in. The middle of.
A series. When I'm going to. Know if I
knowingly shot my. I'm tripping
on nothing or not get it out of
this one. I've got it I've got it
I've got it I've got it I've got it
I've got. The East.
The
in.
The sense.
Of the
the from
. Of course. Of.
The rules on the economy.
In
a. Haiku the AN it is hot on
on the.